<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Journals by Emily]]></title><description><![CDATA[Journals by Emily]]></description><link>http://journalsbyemily.com</link><image><url>images/Cover.png</url><title>Journals by Emily</title><link>http://journalsbyemily.com</link></image><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 23:14:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://journalsbyemily.com/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title><![CDATA[How to start a bullet journal]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div id="preamble">
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<img src="http://journalsbyemily.com/images/Cover.png" alt="Cover.png">
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect3">
<h4 id="_hello_everyone">Hello everyone!</h4>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Welcome to Journals by Emily. I&#8217;m a novice bullet journaler that loves beer, disney, corgis and organization. I caught onto the bullet journaling craze about 7 months ago in June of 2016. I&#8217;ve always been a pretty organized person, but I can tell you that having a bullet journal is a game-changer! I&#8217;m here to say that anyone and everyone who has a passion for living a more organized and structured life can be a bullet journaler.</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<img src="http://journalsbyemily.com/images/how%20to%20start.png" alt="how%20to%20start.png">
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Here is the ultimate list of everything you need to start a bullet journal:</p>
</div>
<div class="olist arabic">
<ol class="arabic">
<li>
<p>a pen</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>a notebook</p>
</li>
</ol>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><strong>That&#8217;s it!</strong></p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Seriously, no joke, that is literally everything you need to have a successful bullet journal.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>There are lots of extra things you can have to make your bullet journal more decorative or fancy, but really the only two things you need is any size notebook, and any kind of writing utensil.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>When I first started bullet journaling I went to Target and bought a blank moleskin sketchpad notebook. I wanted something without lines, because I know it would annoy me to see lines that weren&#8217;t being used in the actual layout. This is the <a href="https://www.amazon.com/Moleskine-Sketchbook-Large-Classic-Notebooks/dp/8883701151/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8&amp;qid=1483927136&amp;sr=8-1&amp;keywords=moleskine+sketchbook">first notebook</a> I used. It lasted me until the end of December, just in time to start a new one for the New Year. I liked the size of this notebook, it wasn&#8217;t too small but still fit in my purse easily, and the pages were thick enough, that there wasn&#8217;t any bleeding. However, any kind of spare notebook you have lying around will work; lined, blank, dotted, whatever, just something to write on!</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Obviously, there are also many different kinds of pens out there that you can use as well. If you get really serious into bullet journaling you may want to later invest in nicer pens with different colors, but until then any pen, pencil, crayon, marker, etc. will work. I do highly recommend these <a href="https://www.amazon.com/Sharpie-Retractable-Point-Black-3-Count/dp/B002ONCFF4/ref=sr_1_4?s=office-products&amp;ie=UTF8&amp;qid=1483928077&amp;sr=1-4&amp;keywords=sharpie+pen">Sharpie Pens</a> that I discovered when I first started bullet journaling. They write nicely, have an awesome retractable top instead of a cap, and don&#8217;t bleed. They&#8217;re my favorite!</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>After you have your supplies all your need to do is write. Write down what you want to organize, write down the days of the week with appointments and birthdays. Write down important dates that you can&#8217;t forget! Make lists of tv shows you want to watch. Make a list for your groceries. It doesn&#8217;t matter, anyway you decide to organize it, and anything you decide to organize is completely up to <strong>you</strong>!</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The point is, anyone can have a bullet journal. It&#8217;s not as complicated as you may think. The great thing about bullet journals is it can keep you organzied in every manner of your life; work, home, fitness, and everything inbetween. Regular planners and agendas only deal with day to day life, but having your own customizable bullet journal can keep you organized in every single aspect of your life.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>I&#8217;ll be here to show you all the amazing ways a bullet journal can keep you organized and on top of everything in your life. Keep visiting my blog and my instagram @journalsbyemily to see the different things a bullet journal can help you with every <em>single</em> day of your newly organized life!</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><em>*This post contains affiliate links. This means if you purchase something by using one of the links above I recieve a very small commission, but at no extra cost to you. I&#8217;ll never post or endorse anything that I haven&#8217;t personally used and loved myself.</em> :)</p>
</div>
</div>]]></description><link>http://journalsbyemily.com/2017/01/15/How-to-start-a-bullet-journal.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://journalsbyemily.com/2017/01/15/How-to-start-a-bullet-journal.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>