<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Untitled RSS Feed]]></title><description><![CDATA[Untitled RSS Feed]]></description><link>http://journalsbyemily.com</link><image><url>images/Intro.png</url><title>Untitled RSS Feed</title><link>http://journalsbyemily.com</link></image><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2017 03:12:03 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://journalsbyemily.com/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title><![CDATA[5 Way to Use Your Bullet Journal to Plan Your Dream Wedding]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div id="preamble">
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<img src="http://journalsbyemily.com/images/blog5.png" alt="blog5.png">
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>180 days from now I will officially be married to my best friend on earth! I&#8217;m naturally a very organized and detailed person, and my job as a photo stylist has made this part of my personality even more attuned to details and an overall vision, so planning a wedding has challenged me in a whole new perspective. I obviously had big plans for what I wanted for my wedding day, pinning the impossible on Pinterest day after day. However, the closer we get to the wedding date the more realistic I become with how I envision my wedding and have had to throw a lot of my crazier dreams out the window. I use my bullet journal everyday, so obviously at some point planning my wedding was going to become a large part of my bullet journal life. So far I have incorporated my wedding planning into my bullet journal in the following five easy ways.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="__1_the_countdown_page">#1 The Countdown Page</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>I&#8217;ve used countdowns in my bullet journal in the past. However, it&#8217;s difficult to be able to successfully countdown to a certain date, so far in advanced, especially if there are days you miss during the countdown! So for this countdown I put the number of days away from the date in a box in a large font once a month, and use the actual dates of the months to physically countdown with "X&#8217;s".</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<img src="http://journalsbyemily.com/images/Countdown.png" alt="Countdown.png">
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="__2_registry_list">#2 Registry List</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Matthew and I have almost lived together for three years, and where I work, at least once a year we are able to get free things for our home, especially the kitchen. Therefore, when it comes to a gift registry it can get a little difficult to know and remember exactly what we need for our home. I began a gift registry list, organized by category like "kitchen", "bathroom" and "bedroom". This will help me to better understand what we need to register for when we eventually start our wedding registry.</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<img src="http://journalsbyemily.com/images/registrylist.png" alt="registrylist.png">
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="__3_song_list_for_the_wedding_day">#3 Song List for the Wedding Day</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>A large part of our wedding day is the music we choose to play for the most important and impactful parts of our special day. This is also the only thing that I can fully control and don&#8217;t have to settle on. I have a column for every part of the wedding day that would need a specific music selection of our choosing like, the "first dance", the "processional", the "recessional" and the "cake cutting".</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<img src="http://journalsbyemily.com/images/Songlists.png" alt="Songlists.png">
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="__4_live_pinterest_board">#4 Live Pinterest Board</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>My favorite pages of my bullet journal that I have made for wedding planning, so far, is what I like to call the "Live Pinterest Board". Obviously, I pinned many different ideas on my wedding Pinterest board and after awhile everything became a little overwhelming and confusing. After deciding on a more clear overall theme and feel for our wedding day I printed all of the ideas and taped them into my bullet journal in a creative but organized manner. This also helps me to understand and remember certain things I need to buy, borrow or find for our wedding day, such as old windows that I plan on using to display our seating chart. Putting all of these picture ideas and a rough layout for our reception helps me to understand the look and feel for our wedding.</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<img src="http://journalsbyemily.com/images/weddingplanning1.png" alt="weddingplanning1.png">
</div>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<img src="http://journalsbyemily.com/images/weddingplanning2.png" alt="weddingplanning2.png">
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="__5_wedding_timeline">#5 Wedding Timeline</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>This is a basic wedding to-do list however it&#8217;s organized by how many months away from the wedding they need to be accomplished. I love a good to-do list, and this specific list is everything I need to ultimately do before our wedding day in 180 days! Organizing it by months from the wedding helps me to prioritize what needs to be done now and what can wait till later. I assembled this list based off lists from Pinterest, The Knot and WeddingWire.</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<img src="http://journalsbyemily.com/images/Weddingtimeline.png" alt="Weddingtimeline.png">
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>These are just 5 easy ways that I use my bullet journal to plan my wedding. I know there are many more ways out there and would love to hear your ideas! If you would like to share your bujo wedding planning ideas with me, please use the hashtag #WedPlanWithEm on Instagram.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Make sure you follow me on instagram @journalsbyemily and be sure to leave me a comment and let me know you stopped by the blog!</p>
</div>
</div>]]></description><link>http://journalsbyemily.com/2017/02/12/5-Way-to-Use-Your-Bullet-Journal-to-Plan-Your-Dream-Wedding.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://journalsbyemily.com/2017/02/12/5-Way-to-Use-Your-Bullet-Journal-to-Plan-Your-Dream-Wedding.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Simple Ways to Meal Plan in your Bullet Journal]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div id="preamble">
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<img src="http://journalsbyemily.com/images/blog4.png" alt="blog4.png">
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Meal planning is something I have always strived to be successful at, but until I understood how to completely plan it out with my bullet journal, I was not successful at all. Unfortunately in the past a lot of food waste has been done by me and my fiance Matthew. However, now with my bullet journal, I can meal plan like a pro! My next goal is meal prepping, but that&#8217;s a whole other ball game!</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="__1_make_a_master_grocery_list">#1 Make a Master Grocery List</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>This is something I found on Pinterest, and had to do! Make a Master Grocery list with categorized lists that help you keep all of your cooking needs organized. The categories I used are; fruits, veggies, dairy, meats, canned, pantry, condiments/sauces, frozen, spices and bakery. I also made lists for easy go-to dinners and lunch/snack ideas as a reference guide for when I am making my meal plan for the week.</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<img src="http://journalsbyemily.com/images/mastergrocerylist.png" alt="mastergrocerylist.png">
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="__2_use_a_simple_dinner_plans_chart_in_your_weekly_spreads">#2 Use a Simple Dinner Plans Chart in Your Weekly Spreads</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Doing something as simple as planning your dinners for the week, by inserting a chart in your weekly spread, can really make quite a difference. This allows you to look at your week ahead at a glance and plan accordingly.</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<img src="http://journalsbyemily.com/images/simpledinnerplan.png" alt="simpledinnerplan.png">
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="__3_add_a_section_for_your_grocery_list_when_meal_planning">#3 Add a Section for Your Grocery List when Meal Planning</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>In this spread I&#8217;ve implemented the same idea as my Master Grocery List, by making a list of simple breakfast and lunch ideas, to help get an idea for grocery needs. I&#8217;ve made a chart to plan my dinners for the week ahead and also added a space for a grocery list. I try to go grocery shopping on Sundays and planning my week ahead of time helps me have a better idea of what I really need, so I can avoid as much food waste as possible.</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<img src="http://journalsbyemily.com/images/grocerylist.png" alt="grocerylist.png">
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="__4_add_a_have_and_a_need_column_next_to_your_grocery_list">#4 Add a Have and a Need Column Next to Your Grocery List</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>For most people simply adding a grocery list when meal planning will be helpful enough. However, for some people, like me, especially when trying a new recipe, it makes everything much easier to write down all the ingredients and decide what you need and don&#8217;t need before going to the grocery store. You never know when you&#8217;re fiance is going to use the rest of the butter and not let you know before you go grocery shopping (am I right?!). I simply use an X to mark what I have and make a square for the things I need, and I&#8217;ll color in the squares once I buy each ingredient.</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<img src="http://journalsbyemily.com/images/haveandneed.png" alt="haveandneed.png">
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="__5_mark_your_meals_with_symbols_for_leftovers">#5 Mark Your Meals with Symbols for Leftovers</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>After a couple of weeks of meal planning with my bullet journal, I started being successful at having dinner ready each night. However, I noticed that many times a lot of our leftovers had gone to waste because we actually had too much food. I kept making dinner and the lunches I had planned without using our leftovers and in the end had to throw them out. So implementing a symbol for meals I have to cook and meals that will be leftovers helps me to not only not waste food but to also not waste money! For this chart I use a purple triangle for the meals I have to make and a black triangle for any meals I&#8217;m having as leftovers. I think next time I&#8217;ll use colors that will contrast more.</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<img src="http://journalsbyemily.com/images/leftovers.png" alt="leftovers.png">
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>I hope these meal planning ideas will help you be a successful meal planner. Once you have really nailed down a system, meal planning can help you not only save money, but also help to not waste as much food and will most likely help you to eat healthier in the end!</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Do you have any meal planning ideas you&#8217;d like to share?! Tag my in your instagram photos with the hastag #mealplanningwithEm</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Make sure you follow me on instagram @journalsbyemily and be sure to leave me a comment and let me know you stopped by the blog!</p>
</div>
</div>]]></description><link>http://journalsbyemily.com/2017/02/05/5-Simple-Ways-to-Meal-Plan-in-your-Bullet-Journal.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://journalsbyemily.com/2017/02/05/5-Simple-Ways-to-Meal-Plan-in-your-Bullet-Journal.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Make a Successful Monthly Layout]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<img src="http://journalsbyemily.com/images/Blog3.png" alt="Blog3.png">
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Welcome back everybody! This week I&#8217;m going to be discussing my monthly layout for the month of February. I typically put my calendar, habit tracker, and monthly to-do list on the same spread. However, this month I decided to change it up and make my calendar for February large enough to fill the entire spread. I want to be able to write my gratitude for each day in my calendar days on my monthly spread rather than in a list format.</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<img src="http://journalsbyemily.com/images/FebMonthly.png" alt="FebMonthly.png">
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>My weekly spread is much different from January. I have made one page dedicated to each day, combining Saturday and Sunday into just the "Weekend". The other half of my spread has a habit tracker for only those seven days (rather than the whole month), a spending tracker, water tracker, sleep tracker, to-do list, need to buy list, a dinner planning chart, and a step tracker. Unfortunately, I messed up on step tracker and set it up for entire month, instead of just these specific seven days, like the rest of the trackers, and&#8230;&#8203; I also totally messed up the dates of the first 3 days on the first page. Whoops&#8230;&#8203; brain fart!</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>For this month, I completely got rid of the meal tracker. I found it too obnoxious to write every single thing down that I eat, and I don&#8217;t think it really encouraged me to eat any healthier than normal. However, I did include a dinner plans chart to help us plan for groceries, and keep us from eating out as often.</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<img src="http://journalsbyemily.com/images/Februaryweekly.png" alt="Februaryweekly.png">
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The last spread that I made for the month of February is my exercise log and planner. One page has a monthly calendar spread with an exercise plan for each day. I designated leg days, arm days, ab days, and specified Saturday as a stretch and yoga day. I only filled in one week to show my ultimate plan for each day and left the rest of the days blank in case I decide I need to do less or more of a specific exercise based on how hard or easy I find it. This allows me to push myself but not give myself unrealistic goals. The other page of this spread is my exercise log. Since I live in Michigan, and the weather in February is typically terrible, I&#8217;m giving myself three cardio options for each day; our indoor bike, walking the dogs, or running outside. Therefore I can keep track of my cardio and make sure it&#8217;s designated to each specific exercise. This also allows me to compare distance and time for each type of cardio rather than trying to distinguish between a walk and a run, for instance. I like having the freedom of different cardio options and being able to see how I&#8217;ve improved or haven&#8217;t improved at just a glance.</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<img src="http://journalsbyemily.com/images/FebExerciseLog.png" alt="FebExerciseLog.png">
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Those are my pages for the month of February. My goal for February is to try and show my love and gratitude to others more often and to focus on getting stronger and more fit. Hopefully these pages that I&#8217;ve set-up will help me to focus on each of my goals and keep me organized in the process. What other spreads could I set-up each month? Do you have any go-to spreads that help you stay organized every month? Leave me a comment on my instagram <strong>@journalsbyemily</strong> and let me know!</p>
</div>]]></description><link>http://journalsbyemily.com/2017/01/29/How-to-Make-a-Successful-Monthly-Layout.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://journalsbyemily.com/2017/01/29/How-to-Make-a-Successful-Monthly-Layout.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A Beginner's Guide to Making a Weekly Layout]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div id="preamble">
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<img src="http://journalsbyemily.com/images/Blog2.png" alt="Blog2.png">
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Welcome everyone! Today I&#8217;ll be discussing the basics to weekly layouts in your bullet journal. Personally, my weekly pages are the most important pages to me. They keep me organized and on track with my specific goals, especially goals that I may be tracking the overall progress of on a separate page.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The first thing you want to do when starting a weekly layout is decide what is the most important thing for you to track and be aware of each week. For instance, I always have a box that has a list of all of the things I want to accomplish that week. Then I separate each to do into different days, ensuring  they&#8217;re all scheduled to be done, but can also be moved to the next day if that specific "to-do" was not accomplished on that specific day. Below I posted a photo of six different weekly layouts that I used in my bullet journal last year.</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<img src="http://journalsbyemily.com/images/blog2-1.png" alt="blog2 1.png">
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Most weeks I use two pages for my weekly layouts but sometimes I only use one. Sometimes I have my food diary on my weekly pages, but other times I make an entirely new page for my food log. I found it extremely helpful this past summer/fall, when I was attempting to get back into good running shape, to look at the weather for the week ahead and plan what days I would run outside and when my rest days would be, based on the weather. However, if you live in an unpredictable climate location, like myself in Michigan, than you know there is only so much planning you can do around the weather. Sometimes I kept a gratitude tracker on each weekly page, but other times, like this month for instance, I used an entire page to track my gratitude for the whole month. I always try to track my water intake cause that&#8217;s something I definitely struggle with, and am always trying to improve. I also quickly changed my habit tracker from being on my weekly pages to my monthly overview page, and I like that a lot more!</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect3">
<h4 id="_let_s_get_started">Let&#8217;s get started!</h4>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The main idea behind weekly layouts is to conform it to your own needs. Maybe you&#8217;re trying to save money so you track how much you spend each week. Or perhaps you want your weekly layouts to be designated only to appoinments, to-do&#8217;s and plans for that week. That&#8217;s great too! The layouts can always change week by week, and you can always change your needs from one week to the next as well. Below I&#8217;ll show you how my layout has changed for the past four weeks in January based on my own needs and my likes, and dislikes from the previous week&#8217;s layout.</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<img src="http://journalsbyemily.com/images/blogweek1.png" alt="blogweek1.png">
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>This is my layout for the first week of January. This year I&#8217;m trying to save money and be more healthy. Therefore, I have a weekly spending tracker, sleep tracker and a daily water tracker. I also have a to-do&#8217;s box for the current week, for the next week, and a box to keep track of necessary items to buy, like grocery items or shampoo.</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<img src="http://journalsbyemily.com/images/blogweek2.png" alt="blogweek2.png">
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>This is for the second week of January. I started a food log this week to help remind myself to eat healthy, and to limit eating out. However, I didn&#8217;t feel like I had enough room to write what I ate for each meal. I hate having to write small!</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<img src="http://journalsbyemily.com/images/blogweek3.png" alt="blogweek3.png">
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Here is the 3rd week of January. I made the food log longer, but not really bigger and I still struggled with room and having to write small. This was probably my least favorite week, in life, and with my layout (it was a longggg week). My to-do box was too long and short so I had to write small, with multiple columns, which I hate to do. I also apparantly made my spending box way too big, since I only filled in one line, so it looks really empty, which is good in real life, but annoying when I look at my pages. I haven&#8217;t been happy with my water log area for the past 3 weeks. My goal is 100 oz. of water a day and I have a 20 oz. water bottle, so I only need 5 squares or circles to fill in, and what I had was just too long, so it always looked awkward, even if I happened to accomplished 100 oz. of water, which I never came close to doing (I&#8217;m telling you, it was a long week!).</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<img src="http://journalsbyemily.com/images/blogweek4.png" alt="blogweek4.png">
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Here is the fourth and final full week of January. I think this will definitely be my favorite weekly layout for this month, I think I worked out the kinks for a lot of my problems. I put my food log in each day instead of having it&#8217;s own table. I made my water log like my sleep log, so it&#8217;s more like a graph, which I think I&#8217;m going to love! I also think that my boxes for "To Do This Week", "Spending", "To Buy", and "To Do Next Week" will be about the right sizes for my needs. We shall see! I&#8217;ll post my finished week on instagram <strong>@journalsbyemily</strong>, and let you know how it worked out for me.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>There are many ways to do a weekly layout, but the important thing to remember, is ultimately your weekly layout is designed towards your specific wants and needs. Having everything you want to track and organize in each weekly layout is more important than having the most beautiful weekly layouts with the best design. Do not compare yourself to others when bullet journaling. If you are like me, you started bullet journaling to live a more organized and succesful lifestyle, not to win any artistic awards for doodles or calligraphy. Also, remember practice makes perfect! Just look at all of my weekly layouts from last year, compared to this year. There is quite a difference!</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Can anyone guess which layout was my very first layout from my first bullet journal? Comment on my instagram <strong>@journalsbyemily</strong> with your guesses!</p>
</div>
</div>]]></description><link>http://journalsbyemily.com/2017/01/22/A-Beginners-Guide-to-Making-a-Weekly-Layout.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://journalsbyemily.com/2017/01/22/A-Beginners-Guide-to-Making-a-Weekly-Layout.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How to start a bullet journal]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div id="preamble">
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<img src="http://journalsbyemily.com/images/Cover.png" alt="Cover.png">
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect3">
<h4 id="_hello_everyone">Hello everyone!</h4>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Welcome to Journals by Emily. I&#8217;m a novice bullet journaler that loves beer, disney, corgis and organization. I caught onto the bullet journaling craze about 7 months ago in June of 2016. I&#8217;ve always been a pretty organized person, but I can tell you that having a bullet journal is a game-changer! I&#8217;m here to say that anyone and everyone who has a passion for living a more organized and structured life can be a bullet journaler.</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<img src="http://journalsbyemily.com/images/how%20to%20start.png" alt="how%20to%20start.png">
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Here is the ultimate list of everything you need to start a bullet journal:</p>
</div>
<div class="olist arabic">
<ol class="arabic">
<li>
<p>a pen</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>a notebook</p>
</li>
</ol>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><strong>That&#8217;s it!</strong></p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Seriously, no joke, that is literally everything you need to have a successful bullet journal.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>There are lots of extra things you can have to make your bullet journal more decorative or fancy, but really the only two things you need is any size notebook, and any kind of writing utensil.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>When I first started bullet journaling I went to Target and bought a blank moleskin sketchpad notebook. I wanted something without lines, because I know it would annoy me to see lines that weren&#8217;t being used in the actual layout. This is the <a href="https://www.amazon.com/Moleskine-Sketchbook-Large-Classic-Notebooks/dp/8883701151/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8&amp;qid=1483927136&amp;sr=8-1&amp;keywords=moleskine+sketchbook">first notebook</a> I used. It lasted me until the end of December, just in time to start a new one for the New Year. I liked the size of this notebook, it wasn&#8217;t too small but still fit in my purse easily, and the pages were thick enough, that there wasn&#8217;t any bleeding. However, any kind of spare notebook you have lying around will work; lined, blank, dotted, whatever, just something to write on!</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Obviously, there are also many different kinds of pens out there that you can use as well. If you get really serious into bullet journaling you may want to later invest in nicer pens with different colors, but until then any pen, pencil, crayon, marker, etc. will work. I do highly recommend these <a href="https://www.amazon.com/Sharpie-Retractable-Point-Black-3-Count/dp/B002ONCFF4/ref=sr_1_4?s=office-products&amp;ie=UTF8&amp;qid=1483928077&amp;sr=1-4&amp;keywords=sharpie+pen">Sharpie Pens</a> that I discovered when I first started bullet journaling. They write nicely, have an awesome retractable top instead of a cap, and don&#8217;t bleed. They&#8217;re my favorite!</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>After you have your supplies all your need to do is write. Write down what you want to organize, write down the days of the week with appointments and birthdays. Write down important dates that you can&#8217;t forget! Make lists of tv shows you want to watch. Make a list for your groceries. It doesn&#8217;t matter, anyway you decide to organize it, and anything you decide to organize is completely up to <strong>you</strong>!</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The point is, anyone can have a bullet journal. It&#8217;s not as complicated as you may think. The great thing about bullet journals is it can keep you organzied in every manner of your life; work, home, fitness, and everything inbetween. Regular planners and agendas only deal with day to day life, but having your own customizable bullet journal can keep you organized in every single aspect of your life.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>I&#8217;ll be here to show you all the amazing ways a bullet journal can keep you organized and on top of everything in your life. Keep visiting my blog and my instagram @journalsbyemily to see the different things a bullet journal can help you with every <em>single</em> day of your newly organized life!</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><em>*This post contains affiliate links. This means if you purchase something by using one of the links above I recieve a very small commission, but at no extra cost to you. I&#8217;ll never post or endorse anything that I haven&#8217;t personally used and loved myself.</em> :)</p>
</div>
</div>]]></description><link>http://journalsbyemily.com/2017/01/15/How-to-start-a-bullet-journal.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://journalsbyemily.com/2017/01/15/How-to-start-a-bullet-journal.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>